[ Watch on kissFlix.co ]
O-Con.
Yes? Yes?
Let's get married.
Yes.
What?
Let's get married.
Huh?
Kekkon?
Marriage.
Wait, by "kekkon" you mean
the dark blood at a crime scene
that splashes everywhere?
[*"Bloodstain" sounds like]
That'd be a bloodstain.
[*"marriage" in Japanese]
Oh, sorry. Please, continue.
- No, no, no, no.
- You go get changed too, Mr. Hirose.
Go get changed. Hello?
Thank you for your continued support.
- Why get married?
- What do you mean, 'why'?
Because I love you, O-Con.
L-L-Lo... That 'love'...
Is it like loving Berry, or loving Tuesla?
- That same kind of...
- No, no, no.
The heart-squeezing kind,
the stomach-twisting kind.
Stomach-twisting...
So it's that kind of love.
I mean, I was away from you for a few days,
but then we had this miraculous reunion.
I just didn't want to be apart.
So I figured, "Marriage, then."
"You must hold on tight to what you love."
My grandma just said that.
It's just too sudden.
Oh, so you mean you need time to think?
Sure, think about it. Go ahead.
- Ten, nine, eight...
- Wait, hold on!
- Seven, six, five...
- What am I supposed to think? Wait!
- Four, three, two...
- Wait, wait, wait! What?
- One, zero.
- What?
- Let's get married.
- No way!
- Oh.
- What do you mean, 'oh'?
I should be the one saying 'oh'!
This is huge! This is huge!
Well, compared to a marriage proposal,
I'm not sure which is bigger.
I guess it's a toss-up, but still.
- But a marriage proposal is still...
- What happened?
The merch shop just called.
They said that inquiries
about Tuesla are flooding in!
- Huh?
- They want to place an additional order!
- Oh!
We need to get things organized quickly.
- I'm off.
- Right. Let's get organized.
Let's get everything organized.
So, your homework. An answer.
Home...
Why?
I already told you, no way.
Fifty Tueslas, right? Thank you.
However, we're currently
- unable to keep up with production.
- Please, do what you can.
- Hey, are you okay?
- I'm so sorry.
- Here, propolis is good for your throat.
- Thank you.
- Yes. Thank you.
- Here's some propolis for you guys too.
- Proposal...
- Thank you.
Oh, be careful. That's really heavy.
[*"Really" sounds like]
'Marriage' heavy?
[*"marriage" in Japanese]
We now have over 100,000 followers
on Chirp Wave!
- What?
- What? Amazing!
- Wow! Amazing!
- Wow, amazing!
[Just looking at it is healing.]
Come on!
[A slow-burn kind of cuteness.]
Congratulations.
[Cute? I watched the video.]
Thanks. Amazing.
[He's just a guy who's not a mooch, lol.]
100,000.
- Wow.
- Amazing. 100,000.
Quick! Someone, take his phone away!
What are you doing?
Mr. Seo was replying to negative comments!
Geez.
It was just a reply.
"Oh, yeah, yeah. Saying something
different from everyone else,
like you want to be special, huh?"
"Finding your place in the world,
good for you."
That's not just a reply. It's a provocation.
From today on, I'll handle the updates
on the official secret account.
Please stop looking at social media, Mr. Seo.
Whatever you do, don't look at it.
Okay.
Because there will be
even worse comments in the future.
Of course, that's kind of proof
that you're getting popular.
It's a side effect of having
more people who like you.
Hello, this is Kusakabe.
Huh?
T-T-The Ministry of Economy,
Trade and Industry?
[2035 Animal Expo]
Tuesla as an ambassador?
Yes, for the Animal Expo held in 2035.
If you could lend your support
as the bid ambassador...
We'll do it. Please let us do it.
Tuesla can be a help to
everyone on the world stage.
That would be so wonderful.
Then, once again, thank you for your support.
Thank you for your support as well.
Also, since this is a public project,
the public scrutiny will be intense.
Please be especially careful to
avoid any problematic behavior.
Problematic behavior?
[It's gotten so popular all of a sudden, lol.
What's so good about it?]
[No, I just don't get the cuteness.]
Oh, no, you're looking at social media again.
We already said you can't do that.
Please rest assured.
Our company's motto is
'zero problematic behavior'.
At today's regular meeting,
the major shareholders are also...
Due to the recent worsening performance,
the stock price has plummeted!
Starting with Harsh Review Molco's scandal,
then Docchicchi's failure,
and then the blunder at
the Character Grand Prix,
everything you do just backfires, doesn't it?
You're the cause of all of this,
aren't you, Mr. Omishima?
If this continues, we'll have no choice
but to ask you to resign.
I apologize for causing concern.
But please rest assured.
The next move is already in motion.
I've made many wrong decisions.
The feelings of those who support us,
and even the feelings of the characters,
I've neglected them.
So I think it's only natural
that I face the consequences.
However,
Molco hasn't done anything wrong.
Omishima.
[Emergency Press Conference]
I couldn't
[by Merry President Omishima]
make Molco happy.
So...
in order to make Molco happy,
I've made the decision to part ways.
Part ways? With what?
What do you mean by 'part ways'?
We, Merry,
will transfer the rights to Cynical Molco.
Huh?
[Episode 8]
I can't believe they're
transferring Molco's rights.
If you give up the rights to a character,
you won't get the profits
if it becomes a hit later.
Even more importantly, the character...
You don't know how it'll be treated.
What do you mean, 'how'?
In cases like this, the rights
go to the highest bidder.
And if it's a shady company,
they might use the character to
advertise shady pots or something.
Well, to be honest,
I don't really care what
happens to Cynical Molco.
Means so much.
Ever since Mr. Omishima became president,
Merry has made a V-shaped recovery.
Well, but, you know... How do I put it...
But look, Mr. Omishima is saying
[Announcing the transfer]
that it's for Molco's sake.
[of Cynical Molco's rights]
Look.
- See these tears.
- I cherish it more than anyone.
I don't think this is a lie.
This is an act.
An act?
Like, those tears that look like
they're about to fall but don't?
- Excuse me.
- Yes.
At the previous celebration for
Molco's movie adaptation,
a drunk Mr. Omishima muttered
that he was into acting
and was good at crying scenes.
Really? That's news to me.
What I heard was a drunk Mr. Omishima
muttering that he was into gospel music.
- What's true about Mr. Omishima...
- Lies, lies. All lies.
That's the kind of guy he is. This too.
We won't choose the winning bidder
based on the size of the offer.
We'll choose based on
how much they love Molco here,
and what they'll do to make Molco happy.
As for Molco's new partner,
I'd like to select them through
a live broadcast open competition.
An open competition, of all things.
Is that like a reality show?
I mean, someone who's genuinely
worried about Cynical Molco
would never do something like this.
He's full of lies. He's Mr. Lie-mishima.
Looking at this, opinions on social media
are split right down the middle.
Some say he's just selling it for money
and are telling him not to make it
sound like a heartwarming story,
while others say he's admirable
for sacrificing so much for Molco.
Indeed.
The loss from giving up Cynical Molco,
the backbone of Merry, is real.
And yet he says he wants Molco to be happy.
He's doing this very skillfully.
[Labravo's Bravo Journey]
The shareholders contacted us just now.
They're asking if it's really okay
to let go of Cynical Molco.
Then, I have a question as well.
Who was it that brought Merry back
from the brink of bankruptcy
in a V-shaped recovery?
It was you, Mr. Omishima.
Then, who is causing
the stock price to plummet now?
Don't hold back.
- It's you, Mr. Omishima.
- That's right.
In other words, the company Merry
is entirely dependent on me.
What's important isn't the characters,
but Takumi Omishima.
Indeed.
With this open competition,
I plan to restore Merry's cohesion
and create a new hit product.
Cynical Molco is just material for that.
Sorry to keep you waiting.
Mr. Morita.
[Trend Up TV Producer]
Actually, there's something I'd like to do.
[Tatsuyuki Morita]
Oh, what is it? Let's hype it up.
There's someone I'd like to have
participate in this open competition.
[Exclusive Interview with]
Are there any conditions
[Merry President Takumi Omishima]
for this transfer of rights?
[In-depth look at the highly anticipated]
No, there aren't any conditions.
[open competition]
If I find a person whom I think is right,
I'll hand over all rights
to them unconditionally.
What do you mean, 'all rights'?
That means everything,
including this production process.
I see.
And the judge will be you, Mr. Omishima?
Look, here, here, here!
Full Tummy Molco is clearly shown!
This is...
Full Tummy Molco is being used
as a character to advertise shady pots.
[Apply here]
I'll take it back!
- No, wait... Don't!
- Hey!
- Let go!
- If you act like that on a live broadcast,
it'll immediately be problematic behavior!
[2035 Animal Expo, Tutu-Tuesla]
And if that happens, our dream
of bringing Tuesla to everyone
could be cut short!
So you're going to
make Molco sell shady pots?
The pot thing is just an example!
I mean!
In the first place,
this kind of selling off... is just sad.
I kind of get it too.
I know there are times
when rights and stuff are a thing.
But somehow,
I just can't help but think that it's sad.
Full Tummy Molco, Cynical Molco.
Let's enter.
The open competition.
Let's definitely enter it.
- But...
- With Seo Design's
overflowing love for its characters,
let's go save Full Tummy Molco,
Cynical Molco, and everyone else!
That's right. Let's enter.
Yes, let's enter.
- O-Con, let's get married...
- But only on one condition...
Which is, no scandals allowed.
With regard to rescuing the Molcos
and succeeding in Tuesla's
expo ambassador role,
we aim to achieve both.
And so for that, the plan
we're launching this time is...
[Highly Confidential]
the Mizuki Seo Completion Plan.
Let's do it. Let's complete him.
He's full of deficiencies, after all.
Huh? I don't have any deficiencies.
I'm not deficient.
Mizuki Seo, the world's most
perfect man. Mizuki Seo...
[Seo Design]
First, can you tell us
why you entered this competition?
Well, it's not like
I like Cynical or anything.
You get it? You get this depth?
Well... but for this competition,
one of the judging criteria
might be how much you like Cynical Molco...
Huh? So you're telling me to lie?
Help! Someone help!
You're just a failed character.
Lie-mishima!
Mr. Seo!
No, no, no! Wait, wait, wait!
Hold on, hold on!
Wait a minute!
Okay, that's enough.
What is this? What are you making me do here?
Sorry, we were in trouble because
we didn't have someone to play Mr. Omishima,
and you showed up just in time,
so I ended up asking you.
Thank you for the refreshments.
Well, they're leftovers, so it's fine.
And now, the scoring.
Minus hell, full marks.
Hell?
I mean, wouldn't just
blurting out Omishima's misdeeds
on the broadcast guarantee a win?
Then just expose how he tricked the designer
and turned Full Tummy Molco
into Cynical Molco, and all that.
But if he plays dumb and ignores it,
you'll just look like a whiner,
and we'll definitely lose the competition.
Exactly. We just have to go head-on.
So, first, the way you're sitting
right now is absolutely no good!
What, are you a soft rice cake or something?
Sit up straight, be sharp!
Also, rambling on is no good.
And first, let's use polite language.
That's basic human decency!
And also, it's no good if you take the bait.
Like earlier, you were
like some huffing beast.
That was so dangerous.
Here we go again! You are
taking away people's individuality,
Japan's future, and the future of
- the Earth that gave birth to us!
- Listen up.
Mr. Omishima said he would judge
based on the fans' voices.
So we have to get those fans on our side.
We have to overwhelm the other candidates
and make them think that Mizuki Seo
should have Molco's rights.
Then even Mr. Omishima
will have no choice but to choose you.
This is no time to whine!
I'm not whining!
Zero Problematic Behavior.
What is that?
- Problem! Sorry!
- Zero Problematic Behavior.
[Planning ability, love, determination.
Who will be chosen?]
[Cynical Molco Proposal Competition]
It seems Peace is starting to make its move
for the competition.
Peace?
Peace Plus, Merry's rival that's ranked
second in the character industry.
[Peace Plus is entering]
It's already trending on social media.
[the open proposal competition!]
It's just a rumor,
but they supposedly have
20 billion yen in reserve funds.
What? So against a company like that,
we have to make people think that
Mizuki Seo is overwhelmingly better?
Exactly. So, it's not just
the Mizuki Seo Completion Plan.
- We also need some strong strategy.
- Then what about this?
This strategy.
Tuesla bread!
Mr. Seo, please focus on the Completion Plan.
Why just me?
Because the Completion Plan is
the fundamental premise for everything.
Fine.
The fundamental premise for everything?
So dramatic.
Everything?
- Strategy...
- Ah!
Could it be... that if
the Completion Plan succeeds,
then we'll be able to get married too?
Is that it? Is that it, O-Con?
Strategy, strategy, strategy...
[No. 1: Cynical Molco Open Competition]
Trending every day.
The competition is getting
a lot of attention.
The shareholders are saying,
"Keep it up like this."
Social media posts about you and Merry
are also starting to get positive reactions.
'Starting to' won't cut it.
Those who are criticizing me
are character fanatics
who love characters excessively.
As for me, they...
Come in.
One, two.
♪ Desu, masu, ossharu, meshiagaru ♪
[*They're all honorifics in Japanese]
♪ Desu, masu, ossharu ♪
- ♪ Meshiagaru ♪
- Omishima!
Help!
- No, no!
Okay, so what do you do when
you feel like turning into a beast?
Molco rescue, Tuesla expo.
- ♪ Desu, masu, ossharu ♪
- No.
- ♪ Meshiagaru ♪
- Help.
- Good! Focus!
- Help!
- ♪ Yes. Desu, masu, ossharu ♪
- ♪ Desu, masu, ossharu ♪
[Open Competition Strategy Plan]
Strategy, strategy, strategy...
No good.
O-Con.
Oh, geez.
Ever since Mr. Seo saw me that time,
I can't focus on singing anymore.
Well, but...
he didn't make fun of me,
the Midnight Closet A Cappella Woman.
He just worried about me.
She'll eat you.
I'm saying! Forget it.
That song from earlier. You can't sleep?
- Your leg cramps from anxiety?
- No! Don't say it!
I don't want to hear it! I've hit my limit!
He's somewhat of a good person.
But that doesn't mean marriage!
- Good work.
- Hey, hey.
I'm doing the final check on the rhythms
of polite language.
Kudasaru, tamawaru, itashikaneru.
What's this 'tamawaru'?
Oh, 'tamawaru'... well, I think
it's basically the same as 'kudasaru'.
Like 'itadaku'.
And 'itashikaneru' means
'won't do it', right?
♪ Kudasaru, tamawaru, itashikaneru ♪
♪ Ah, let's go ♪
♪ Kudasaru, tamawaru, itashikaneru, ah ♪
Wait, wait.
Kudasaru, tamawaru, itashikaneru.
Huh? What are you talking about?
Mr. Seo, that's it! That's it!
Huh? What?
Thank you.
♪ Kudasaru, tamawaru, itashi... ♪
It's rude not to knock, you know.
I want you to cancel
the cancellation of the plushies.
You're Mr. Seo, the designer. Right?
Did you hear me? Mamepon, Kokeko, and Petal,
I want you to cancel the production
cancellation of these plushies.
Considering the current state of the company,
the cancellation is a reasonable decision...
No, don't act like you know
what you're talking about, amateur.
You're just a new character.
What do you know about...
I'm very sorry.
You'll really get fired.
Honestly, these creative types...
Shall we go ahead?
The problem isn't the creators.
I'll have you cause
plenty of problems, Mr. Seo.
It's done.
[Business Portfolio Redesign]
The strategy.
I'm getting goosebumps here.
This is amazing, Ms. Kusakabe.
We can win with this, for sure.
For Molco, for Tuesla. For Molco, for Tuesla.
Molco, Tuesla, Molco, Tuesla.
All right, now let's
practice for the real thing.
[Cynical Molco Proposal Competition]
Nice, it's all hyped up now.
- Good morning.
- Oh, good morning.
- Thank you for everything today.
- It's nicely hyped up.
This is great too.
So this is the atmosphere, right?
Why do you have bedhead today of all days?
Wait, wait, Mr. Seo! That's not tea.
Oh.
So you get nervous too, Mr. Seo?
Hey, just hypothetically, what if we fail?
Then, well, we'll just have to
do what we always do.
- What we always do?
- Because
you've had countless
impossible failures up until now, right?
- Huh? What?
- But each time,
me, Mr. Hirose, Ms. Sasaoka,
and even you yourself
have managed to handle it somehow, right?
It'll work out somehow.
Or rather, I'll make it work out.
So today, just do what you always do. Huzzah!
See? Just like always.
Well, failure is impossible anyway.
We'll definitely succeed.
Right. We'll definitely succeed.
And I'll do it again. The proposal.
All right!
[Who Will Molco End Up With?]
It's finally begun.
The Cynical Molco Proposal Competition.
Who will capture the heart of
this national character?
We'll be watching closely.
And now, here comes today's star,
Cynical Molco!
Molco in a lovely dress.
It appears Molco
is being escorted by the judge
and Merry President Takumi Omishima.
How are you feeling, Molco?
A tear-jerking farewell? Hmph.
First, the candidates will
introduce their companies.
Mr. Omishima has not been informed
of this year's candidates.
It'll be exciting to see who appears.
That's right.
What about Mr. Seo?
And now, the first candidate is entering.
[President and CEO of Peace Plus Co., Ltd.
Kazuo Nimura]
Oh!
Right from the start,
the top favorite appears!
The number two design company
in the character industry,
Peace Plus, and its president,
Mr. Kazuo Nimura.
Today, I'm not here for second place.
I've come to take first place.
Thank you.
[President and CEO of GeToys Co., Ltd.]
For 50 years, our company
[Teppei Takarada]
has been making toys
to bring smiles to children.
What we create are lifelong treasures.
[Account Planner]
We use ideas and communication power,
[Toyo Media Cross Co., Ltd.]
to create major movements in the world
[Seigo Takamiya]
as an advertising agency.
What should we do?
Everyone looks really good.
But for now, Mr. Nimura is still...
It's okay.
Because it's Mr. Seo, I'm sure it'll be okay.
And now, the next candidate.
Appearing from the design office behind
the currently trending Tutu-Tuesla,
[Designer, Seo Design, Mizuki Seo]
it's Mizuki Seo of Seo Design.
I am Mizuki Seo of Seo Design.
He's using polite language?
Flowers will eventually wither.
So, take this.
[Victory confirmed! He's Tuesla's designer?]
[A prince straight out of
a shoujo manga has appeared.]
[Is Tuesla's designer seriously this cool?]
And next, the final candidate will appear.
[Designer, Merry Co., Ltd.]
Please come forward.
[Rena Kawasaki]
Why?
The final candidate is,
surprisingly, Rena Kawasaki!
She is the current chief designer at Merry,
and also the main designer of Cynical Molco.
It seems that Mr. Omishima
didn't know about her participation.
Ms. Mondo always said
that characters are not tools.
They are alive.
I oppose Mr. Omishima's
transfer of Cynical Molco's rights.
If I can obtain its rights,
I will separate all decision-making
authority regarding Molco
from Mr. Omishima and management,
and return it to the creators.
[That red dress suits her too well!
The successor to Mondo-ism!]
[Now this is a character designer!
We've been waiting for someone like this!]
[It's crazy that even
the president didn't know!]
[I kind of want to root for her. Go for it!]
[Carry the next generation of Merry!]
[Kitchen Sakoda]
And that concludes
the company introductions
from the eight candidates,
selected after strict examination.
It's great that
Tuesla became a hit, isn't it?
Thanks.
When you were with us, you were
pretty much unknown, right, Mr. Seo?
Okay, commercial break.
We'll now be taking a short break.
- Thank you.
- Yes. Let's take a break.
Well, then.
- Good work.
Wow, prosciutto and melon,
so elegantly done. Truly a prince.
It's delicious.
The Completion Plan is a huge success!
But Rena's appearance was a bit unexpected.
And in fact, she got the most buzz online.
Hey, hey, how was it? How was it?
Great! Great performance!
Just as the president ordered.
Are we gaining popularity
with the character lovers?
Yeah, yeah, we're gaining.
They're even calling you
the successor to Mondo-ism.
What a relief.
- Relief-ism!
Burn, burn.
Flames, burn.
We'll be resuming shortly.
- Mr. Tokui.
- Yes?
May I borrow a pen?
- Go ahead.
- Thank you.
[Cynical Molco]
The proposal competition
[Final Proposal Competition]
is now starting!
Here, suppose you've acquired
the rights to Cynical Molco.
Please use an image board to show
what kind of business development
you have in mind
to Cynical Molco and to Mr. Omishima,
in the form of a proposal competition.
Are you drawing image boards, Mr. Seo?
Yeah.
I was thinking of making a collage,
so I'm collecting materials. But this one.
Do you know it?
It looks like Cynical Molco,
but it's kind of plain.
And just like someone, it's kind of
unknown, not making a splash.
- That's... That's...
- Huh? So you do know it?
This 'unknown' one.
Oh, wait. Why does the torn one look cuter?
Mr. Seo is about to turn into
a wild beast, isn't he?
Did Rena say something to him?
Oh, come on.
Molco rescue, Tuesla expo, O-Con marriage.
Molco rescue...
That's Full Tummy Molco. Be nice to it.
Why? The president said that
he had a short temper.
[Time remaining]
All right.
Isn't that a bit too fast?
If you're making something
with PowerPoint or AI,
even in this amount of time...
There's no need to rush.
Everything is going as planned.
Oh! Mr. Takarada is already proposing!
[Teppei Takarada]
Please.
Running and stuff? That kind of thing. Hmph.
If you come to us, Molco,
what kind of future will come?
Please listen to the story
of the future we've drawn.
Molco and the Little Toy Shop.
Molco rescue, Tuesla expo, O-Con marriage.
Huh? What was this character's name again?
Ah, Mankitsu Mokugyo, right?
If we can receive Molco's rights,
we'll use our agency's methods
to the fullest,
[Seigo Takamiya]
from jumbo passenger planes
to giant urban visuals.
We'll hijack the media's prime spots
and make them all about Molco.
What was it again? Manmaru Monpe?
Please look over there.
[President and CEO]
The tens of thousands of
[of Strada Logistics Co., Ltd.]
trucks running through town,
[Eiji Kuramochi]
the uniforms, and the cardboard boxes.
[Cynmor Logistics]
We'll fill everything with Molco.
Mongol Turkey?
Itoko to Hatoko?
[People who put their all into
what they love are wonderful]
[The prince looks happy.
He draws with such a nice expression.]
[I can feel the love for the character.
He's most attractive when he's drawing.]
[Time remaining]
And now, there are only 30 minutes left.
Hey, do you think he's okay?
All right.
[Kazuo Nimura]
Here comes Mr. Nimura of Peace Plus.
Please.
If you entrust Cynical Molco to Peace Plus,
we'll invest a total budget of 30 billion yen
and grow Molco into a global brand instantly.
Movies, games, fashion,
and amusement facilities like Molco Land.
We'll establish all that worldwide
and expand Cynical Molco globally.
Could you entrust us with
making this dream a reality?
Thank you. That was
an overwhelming presentation.
[Amazing! 30 billion yen!
Molco will become a world star!]
And now, the remaining time is running out.
Here comes Seo Design!
Thank you.
Mr. Seo, can you tell us about
your business development plan
after acquiring Molco's rights?
We will give up
the exclusive rights to Molco.
What?
I humbly cannot accept
what you have graciously given.
What did that mean? Was that in the script?
No, it wasn't.
But it's okay.
We practiced so much.
So, Mr. Seo, what exactly...
We, Seo Design.
Will make the whole world
fall in love with Cynical Molco.
[Making Molco]
We propose
[Everyone's Property]
making Molco everyone's property.
Make Molco everyone's property.
- Molco... To those who need Molco,
- To those who need Molco,
- we'll open Molco up to everyone.
It's as if Mr. Seo is
becoming like Ms. Kusakabe.
Is this possession? Is he being
possessed by Ms. Kusakabe?
And we won't be the rights holder,
but the representative guardian.
For example, if a hospital wants
to use Molco to comfort children
who are afraid of hospitals,
we'll allow them to use Molco freely
on brochures, wall art, anything.
Also, if a lackluster shopping district
wants to use Molco as its image character
to liven things up,
Molco will rush over.
Of course, all that will be free of charge.
Oh, then what about our place?
Our visitors have decreased,
and the staff is all sad.
Of course.
If you want to use Molco's power
to make someone happy and joyful,
if you want to borrow Molco's power,
we'll happily send Molco out to do that.
However, I think there are also companies
that want to do business with Molco.
In such cases, we'll ask Molco
to receive a salary.
So that way, everyone's plans are feasible.
[I want to ask for Molco to help with
our shop too! That's what I want!]
[The love is so intense it makes me cry.
Seo's stock just skyrocketed.]
[Molco can be a savior for
regional revitalization!]
And among you all, there's this person.
But in that case, Seo Design will ultimately
monopolize the profits
while calling it Molco's salary, won't you?
No.
All salary that Molco receives
belongs only to Molco.
It's not our company's profit.
Instead, it will be used for
Molco's future growth.
Consulting with everyone.
Molco becomes everyone's property.
The more people we have
who cherish Molco that much,
the more we all protect
and nurture Molco together.
That's the proposal from Seo Design.
[Making Molco Everyone's Property]
Interesting.
I'm not convinced!
I'm firmly against the idea of transferring
Cynical Molco's rights to Seo Design!
Everyone's property?
I can't trust that kind of idealistic spin.
Because Seo Design has Ms. Kusakabe.
The problem is Anna Kusakabe,
the consultant who's under contract
with Seo Design.
Can you get her on camera?
Yeah, the one in the gray jacket.
Right, that's her.
Everyone, are you familiar
with Kitchen Sakoda?
It was Ms. Kusakabe's consulting that
made that restaurant a huge success.
But it was also Ms. Kusakabe
who drove the couple running
Kitchen Sakoda to divorce.
Ignoring their wishes
and driving a wedge between them
by prioritizing the numbers and money.
Apparently, that's what caused the divorce.
And I also have more information
that hasn't come to light yet.
The remaining owner ran
the original Kitchen Sakoda alone.
I heard it's closing due to poor performance.
No way.
[Not a consultant, just a homewrecker.]
[Poor Kitchen Sakoda, targeted like that.]
[Are Ms. Kusakabe's other clients okay?]
[Could Seo be sweet-talked?
A divorce would ruin everything.]
Ms. Kusakabe only cares
about money and numbers.
I don't want Molco
anywhere near someone like that.
She doesn't have any love for characters!
Burn, burn.
O-Con doesn't have any love for characters?
Oh, my!
♪ Tuesla, Tutu-Tuesla ♪
Cute.
Don't. Mr. Seo, don't!
I'll never forgive anyone who hurts O-Con!